（寧々）まずいわね。→
This isn't good.
葵姐さんの男鹿に対する態度。
The way Madame Aoi acts toward Oga...
千秋　あんた　どう思う？
Chiaki, what do you think?
（千秋）完…全にホの字ですね。
She's completely... head-over-heels.
あの取り乱し方。
Losing her self-control like that...
（葵）((え？バカバカバカー！))
You stupid, stupid, stupid-face!
まさか姐さん　うちらの掟
忘れたわけじゃないわよね。
Don't tell me she's forgotten our vow?
少し荒れそうね。
I feel a storm brewing.
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから
赤ん坊を育てることになった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語＞
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
＜ただし　その赤ん坊は
普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
魔王の子だったのです＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
Love is a Hurricane!
（古市）
…こ　この裏切り者が～！
You... You two-timing bastard!
（男鹿）はあ？
とぼけんじゃねえ！
Huh?
Don't play dumb, you philanderer!
この浮気も～ん！
ヒルダさんという人がいながら→
You've got Hilda-san, and at the same
time you laid hands on the Queen!
クイーンにまで手ぇ
出しやがって！
アホ　お前と一緒にすんな。
Idiot. Don't take me down to your level.
じゃあ　何なんだよ！
Then what was that, huh?
見ただろう。あの邦枝って女の
すさまじい強さ！
Didn't you see it? That Kuneida
chick was seriously powerful!
ベル坊も珍しく喜んでやがった。
（ベル坊）アーダァ！
Baby Beel was even actually
impressed for a change.
あいつになら絶対なつく！
I'm totally confident he'd
fall in love with her!
((バッブー))
必ずあの女にベル坊を
押し付けてみせる！
I'm gonna shove this baby onto
her if it's the last thing I do!
そしてこんな生活とも
おさらばだ～！
Then I'll say, "See you later,
alligator!" to this life I got now!
ウハハハ！
情けねえ決意だな。おい。
That's some life-goal
you got there... Sheesh.
（ヒルダ）
誰に？何を押し付けるって？
Who? What are you going
to shove off, did you say?
うわあああ。
またミルク忘れてるぞ。
You forgot his milk again.
葵姐さん！
な　なによ。
Madame Aoi!
W-What?
しょう～じきに答えてください！
Answer me straaaaaaaight out.
あの男鹿って奴のこと。
どう思ってます？
What do you think of this Oga guy?
ど　どうって…別に！
T-Think? Nothing much.
うそっすね！昨日から　ずっと→
You're lyin', ain't you?
Haven't you been totally off in
another world since yesterday?
心ここにあらずって
感じじゃないっすか！
ううっ…！
まさか…→
Please don't tell me...
本気でホレたとか言うんじゃ…！
そ　そんなわけ　ないでしょ！
You've actually fallen for him, for real?!
O-Of course not!
ま　まあ　確かにあんな事　言われて
びっくりしたってゆ～か。
Well, I mean... When he said that
to me, I was really surprised...
その…そこまで悪い奴には
見えなかったし。
And I don't actually think
he's all that bad a guy...
うえ！
あの赤ん坊も
ちょっとかわいいな～って。
And that baby is kinda cute, you know?
ダ～メだ　こりゃ～。
Put a fork in 'er. She's done.
で　で　で　でも　ホラ　急に母親って
わけには　いかないじゃない？
B-B-B-But I can't just
become a mother, right?
私　まだ高校生だし　物には順序が。
I'm still in high school. There's
a proper order to these things.
姐さん　まさか　うちらの掟
忘れたわけじゃないっすよね。
Madame, don't tell me you
forgot our vow, right?
あっ…。
男！作るべからず！
Acquire no man!
先々代から受け継がれてきた→
Passed down for two generations,
the tradition of the Red Tails...
レッドテイルの伝統
男が出来る時は辞める時！
When you get a boyfriend, you quit!
それが今までチームの結束を
固めてきた唯一無二の掟です！
That is the one-and-only rule
which has kept the team together.
このままじゃ　下のモンに
示しがつきませんよ。
You won't be able to give orders
to the lower-ranks like this.
ふ…だから言ってるでしょ。
それはないって。
That's why I told you...
It's not like that.
信じて…いいんですね？
I can believe you, right?
ん。
なるほど女か。
Yes.
I see... A woman, is it?
確かに男だろうが女だろうが→
It is true that the master will take to
anyone who is strong, be they man or woman.
強ければ坊っちゃまは
なつくだろうな。
だよな！
んぐんぐ。
Yup!
まだこの学校に　それほどの
人間がいたのか。
I am surprised there was a human of
such caliber still in this school.
一度　会っておきたい。
I'd like to meet her once.
んぐんぐ。
ほらほら坊っちゃま。
Now, now, Master... You're spilling it.
こぼしておりますよ。
《いいなぁ　オレも甘えてみてぇ》
Aww... I want to be pampered, too!
((バブバブ…))
あう！
あい！
誰だよ！空気よめねぇな！
Who was that?! Don't break my mood!
（碇）≪オガヨメ発見～！≫
I spot me an Oga-Wife!
（碇）こんな所で一家団らんか？→
Sure you wanna have happy family
time in a place like this?
油断しすぎだぜ。男鹿。
You've let your guard down too much, Oga.
Ikari
エ　ＭＫ５！
M... MK-5!
あまりの残虐さに
近付く者はいない。
They're so cruel, no one
will even get near them!
というか近付きたくない奴ら。
They're the guys you don't wanna get anywhere
near! The group of five Major Mood-Killers, MK-5!
マジで空気読めない５人組！
ＭＫ５！
キキ！東邦神姫だけが
石矢魔じゃねぇんだよ。
Ishiyama ain't all about the TKKH, you know.
ヨメとガキの命が…あ？
ぎょおおおお！
If you value the life of your wife and kid...
ぐ！
命を惜しむのは貴様らの方だ。
It's you who should value your life...
貴様ら名前は！？
Tell me your name!
ん？碇。
Ikari...
（茶藤）茶藤。
（嶋村）嶋村。
（中田）中田。
Chato!
Shimamura!
Nakata!
（武宇）武宇。
Bu!
I-Instant defeat!
しゅ　瞬殺！
しかも何て理不尽なキャラ紹介！
And what kind of a character
introduction was that?
つーか　オガヨメ　容赦ねえ！
Whoa, Oga's wife don't hold back!
う　うそだろ？
（ゴキゴキ）
Y-You've got to be kiddin' me!
空気よめや～！
Get with the mood!
（碇）ダメだこりゃ～！
Ain't happening!
あの２人…どんどん
息が合ってくよな～。
The two of them seem more and more in sync.
男鹿とＭＫ５が
やりあったらしいぞ。
Looks like Oga did in the MK-5!
マジかよ。あいつら空気よめよ。
Seriously? Those guys
should've read the mood!
ま～た男鹿。
Oga again?
し　仕方ないわね！
What a little troublemaker he is!
ね　姐さん！
かわいい…。
Madame Aoi!
Cute...
ハッ！
《な　何　あの女！》
W-Who is that woman?
これ　やったの
ほとんど女の方だろ？
The woman took out most of 'em, right?
ああ　まさに最凶夫婦だな。
Yeah... They're one seriously
strong husband and wife team.
夫婦！？
Husband and wife?!
夫婦って　どういうこと？
What do you mean by husband and wife?
だから　あのキンパツの
姉ちゃんが男鹿のヨメ。
I mean, that blond girly is Oga's wife.
い～よな～って　おい！→
Nice, huh?
...wait!
邦枝ぁぁ！
It's Kunieda!
へ～そうなんだ。→
So that's how it is...
一度ならず二度までも…。
Not once, but twice?
おのれ！
（不良たち）うげええ！
うちらで　なんとか
するしかないか。
Looks like we've got to do something.
で　男鹿よ。クイーンにベル坊
押し付けるったって→
So, Oga?
How exactly are you going to shove
Baby Beel off onto the Queen?
どうするつもりだよ。
あ？
確かに邦枝は強いけどさ
全然　悪くないじゃん。
It's true that Kunieda is
strong, but she isn't evil.
まさか勝手にベル坊が
なつくと思ってんの？
Did you think Baby Beel would just
take a liking to her on his own?
うっ！古市…→
Furuichi.
男は気合だぜ！
ようするに
ノープランなんだろうが！
Men are all about guts!
So basically you have no plan?
バーカ　女王だぞ　女王！
Idiot! She's the Queen! The Queen!
魔王がなつかね～わけね～って。
A Demon Lord is sure to
fall for her, you betcha!
邦枝のは単なるあだ名だから！
It's a nickname, you know!
（夏目）男鹿ちゃ～ん。
ん？
Oga-chan!
邦枝と　やりあったんだって？
なんだよ　早え～よ。
I hear you went a round with Kunieda?
Over so fast?
見たかったのに～。
I wished I could have watched...
誰？
ほら　神崎と一緒にいた。
Whozat?
You know, the guy that was with Kanzaki.
ま　でも決着つかなかったんだろ？あいつ　つえ～もんな～。
But you didn't actually
decide the winner, right?
She's pretty strong, yeah...
（寧々）男鹿辰巳～。
Oga Tatsumi!
ちょいとツラ貸してもらおうか。
You're coming with us.
アイー？
お～？
ヒルダさん！この人たちの
リーダーがさっき言った…→
Hilda-san! Their leader just
said something about...
あ　あれ？
Huh?
なるほどな。
あ…。
I see.
あ　ああ…。
貴様が邦枝か。一目でわかったぞ。
You are Kunieda, yes?
I could tell just at a glance.
《わ　わかったって！？》
S-She could tell?
《まさか！あのことが
奥さんにバレて…！》
Don't tell me his wife knows about that!
確かに　やりそうだ。
い～え～　やってません！
You definitely sound like you could do it.
No! Not at all!
あの　その　私は別に
そういうつもりじゃ…。
I mean, it wasn't like I was trying to...
まどろっこしい話は抜きだ。
Shall we dispense with
the long-winded speeches?
ハッ！
少々…手合わせ願おうか。
Let us get on with this, already.
話し合いは無理そうね。
It doesn't seem like talking's
going to accomplish anything.
あっ…！
上だ！
From above!
反応は上出来だ。
You have excellent reaction time.
心月流抜刀術　参式！
Shingetsu sword school, third style!
あっ！
面白い！私に抜かせたこと
誇ってよいぞ！
Interesting!
You should feel honored
to have forced me to draw!
（爆発音）
く…。
《あの状態から　かろうじて
かわしたか…》
She just barely dodged, from that position?
《確かに強い…だが→
She is strong.
But unfortunately, not at his level.
残念ながら
あの男ほどではない…か》
（由加）≪姐さん！≫
Madame Aoi!
（由加）大変っす！
（マスク）寧々さんと千秋さんが！
Nana-san and Chiaki-san have been...
え？
あっ。
今　手当てをしたところっす。
They've been treated just now.
誰が？
Who did this?
寧々さんたち　男鹿に
話つけに行くって言って。
Nene-san said she and Chiaki-san
were gonna talk with Oga.
くっ！
おい聞いたか！？男鹿が邦枝の部下２人を半殺しだってよ！
Hey, you here? Oga half-killed
two of Kunieda's girls!
マジかよ！
You kiddin' me?
女相手だろうが容赦ないぜ！
He don't hold back, even 'gainst girls!
（不良）激怒した邦枝とついに
屋上でタイマンだってよ！
Kunieda's seriously pissed!
They're facing off on the roof!
男鹿辰巳…。
Oga Tatsumi...
あんたは許さない。
I won't forgive you.
アーイーダブ！
（不良）男鹿と邦枝が
屋上でタイマンだってよ！
They say Oga and Kunieda's
facin' off on the roof!
I totally wanna watch, but the thunder's
so scary, I can't go outside!
くそ！見に行きたいのに
雷が怖くて外出れね～ぜ！
Hey, you came to me? Better
than I could ask for.
そっちから来てくれるたぁ
気が利くじゃねぇか！
で？何を許さねぇって？
So? What won't you forgive me for?
はっ！
あんたの狙いは私でしょ？
You're aiming for me, right?
だったら最初から
私のところに来なさいよ！
Then come to me first!
Aiming?
狙い？
アゥ…。
何だ　知ってんのかよ。
Oh, you knew?
だったら　話は早えな。
Then that simplifies things.
アダ。
あ…。
Here. Anytime you're ready.
ほい　いつでもど～ぞ。
はぁ！？この期におよんで
まだ赤ん坊を盾にする気？
At a time like this, you
still hide behind your baby?
You fiend!
この卑怯者！
What? You won't take him for free?
なんだ…ただじゃダメってことか。
（邦枝）何したの？
はぁ？
What did you do?
What did you do to them?
（邦枝）２人に何をしたの？
あんなにボロボロになるまで！
For them to be so beat up...
Those two...?
２人？
あ～…弱ぇヤツに用はねえからな。
I don't got any use for weaklings, see.
サクッとぶっ飛ばしただけだぜ。
I just blew them away real quick like.
You villain!
外道が！！
あ…。
Nene-san, you're awake?
寧々さん　気がつきましたか！
あたし…。
I...
あ…。
（猫）ウーッ。
ウィッ。
（猫）シャァァッ。
うぅ～。
アウッ…。
ギャァァ～。
うぅ～。
シャァァッ！
ダダダダ…アダッ！
うりゅ…。
ウ…アウ。
アウ…アウ。
ベル坊～！
Baby Beel!
離れろ　この性悪猫！
Let go, you wicked cat!
ふぅ…。
Uh... Can we fight or something?
あの　ちょっと…勝負。
It's not the time for that!
今　それどこじゃねえよ！
Don't cry, Baby Beel! It's only a light cut!
泣くなベル坊！傷は浅いぞ！
Hey! Wait!
（寧々）あっ　こら　待ちなさ～い！
Don't cry, Baby Beel!
ベル坊　泣くな～！！
なんだ　やんねえのか。
What, not gonna?
What was with him?
何なの　あいつ…。
猫ちゃん　かわいい。
The cat was cute.
（寧々）ったく　肩すかしも
いいところだね。
Man... Looks like he gave us the slip.
But... He really didn't look like a bad guy.
でも確かに　悪い奴じゃ
ないのかも。
Chiaki, you too?
千秋　あんたまで！
That's right. Oga is the pinnacle of evil!
（中田）そうだぜ　男鹿は極悪さ。
葵姐さんは！
Madame Aoi!
Don't worry! She said she was
going to get revenge for you!
安心して下さい。さっき
寧々さんたちの敵を取るって→
On the roof against Oga!
男鹿と屋上に。
え！？
This is bad... If the two of them fight now,
（寧々）《まずい　今２人が
戦ったら→
it'll go exactly as they planned it to!
あいつらの思うつぼだ！》
（寧々）ハァハァ…。
MK-5!
（ＭＫ５）エム　ケイ　ファイブ！
（ＭＫ５）行き止まり～。
Dead end.
You guys really do kill the mood.
ほんっと　空気読めない連中ね。
Oga and Kunieda are facing off?
≪男鹿と邦枝がタイマン？
マジかよ！≫
Seriously?!
Yup, sounds like it.
ああ　そうらしいぜ。
なんでも　男鹿が→
I head Oga beat some of
Kunieda's girls to a pulp!
邦枝の部下をボコったとか。
≪うはっ　そりゃ邦枝もキレるわ≫
（夏目）《ボコった？》
Kunieda ain't gonna stand for that, no way.
Beat up?
（碇）ケケッ　潰し合え　潰し合え！
残った方を→
Crush each other, do it!
And then we'll finish off
whichever one's left!
俺たちが叩き潰す。
うまくいきましたね　美破さん。
It's going great, isn't it, Miwa-san?
（碇）部下の女を
ちょっと　小突いただけで→
Who'd have thought it? Rough her girls up
a bit, and she plays right into our hands.
ここまで予想通りに
事が運ぶとは…。
（美破）んふふ…あの女が
考えてることなら→
I can tell precisely what
that woman is thinking.
私　手にとるように
わかるもの。
Kunieda Aoi...
邦枝葵…愛する者と戦わなければ
ならない苦しみ→
Suffering from having to
fight the one she loves...
たっぷりと味わいなさい。
Savor it.
You're really perceptive noticing Queen
Kunieda fell for Oga like that...
よく気付きましたね。
あのクイーン邦枝が→
男鹿にホレてるなんて…。
Who did you just call "Queen"?
誰が　クイーンですって？
ボキッ…。
（美破）誰が女王か　言ってごらん
って言ってるのよ！→
I said: Who did you just call "Queen"?
Killing the mood as always, damn you!
相変らず空気読めないわね。
I apologize Miwa-san, sir!
（碇）すみません
美破さんです！
That's right.
そうよ　フッ…女王は
２人もいらないわ。
There's no need for two Queens.
なるほどね　こんなムカつくこと
する奴は…美破ね！
I see. Miwa's the asshole who did this!
（ＭＫ５）クク…ご名答。
Bingo.
（寧々）フン　あんたたちの
思い通りになんか…。
I ain't gonna let you guys do...
Hold it!
（茶藤）おっと！
（嶋村）逃がさねえよ。
You aren't escaping.
（中田）ヒヒッ！
ハァハァ…なぜ　どうして
攻撃してこないの？
Why? Why won't you attack?
何考えてるのか知らないけど…。
I don't know what you're thinking,
まだまだ　あの子たちの痛みは
こんなものじゃ　ないわよ！
but you haven't suffered
near the pain those two did!
Shingetsu sword school, first style!
心月流・抜刀術
壱式！→
Rock Shatter!
破岩！菊一文字！
Chrysanthemum Cut!
姐さん！
Madame Aoi!
ククッ…ケリがついたかな？
Sounds like it's over.
こっちも終わりにするか！
Time to finish up here too!
I'm sorry, Madame Aoi...
（寧々）
《すみません姐さん　私が
勝手なこと　したばっかりに》
I was always acting without your orders...
やっぱ　こういうことか。
I figured as much.
Go. I'll be up shortly.
行きな　後はやっとくから。
ううっ…。
一体　何のつもりだ！
What the hell are you doing?
ん～　だってさぁ　お前ら
全然面白くないもん。
Well, you see... You guys aren't fun at all.
アーダ。
（寧々）ハァハァ…姐さん
違うんです。→
Madame Aoi!
You're mistaken! It wasn't Oga!
男鹿じゃないんです！
え？
This was a trap!
（寧々）ワナだったんです。私と
千秋が　やられたのは。
The one who beat up Chiaki and me was...
Checkmate!
（美破）チェックメイトよ。
Miwa!
美破！
どういうこと？
What is going on?
フフ…全ては　あんたと男鹿を
戦わせるためのワナよ。
It was all a trap to make you
and Oga fight each other.
えっ？
And thanks to that, you're barely
standing... That's dangerous, you know.
おかげで　あんたはバテバテ。
まずいわね～→
Could you beat me like you are now, I wonder?
今　私と戦って
勝てるのかしら。
トゥーー！！
Do you have any idea how hard it
was to sit back and take all that?!
人が　せっかく
ガマンしてんのに～！
Get the hell outta my way.
ジャマすんじゃねえぞ。
Ah, that hit the spot.
あ～　すっきり。さあて
男鹿ちゃんたち　どうなったかな？
Now then... How are Oga-chan
and the others doing?
What have you...
なにを…してくれてんのよ
このボケがぁ！
...done to me, you jackass!
And what the hell? Seriously?!
ってゆ～か　何なのあんた
さっきまで　ボコボコに→
Weren't you all beat up like a second ago?
やられてたくせに
空気読みなさいよ！
Get with the mood already, jeez!
こっから先は　女王対決でしょ！
そ～ゆう流れ　わっかんないかなぁ！
We were about to have a battle
to decide who's Queen!
Don't you see how these things go?!
Damn it all! I can't believe you!
あ～もう　ほんと信じらんない！
How dare you do this to my beautiful face!
私の美しい顔を　よくも
絶対ぶっ…。
I am so going to...
Say what?
なに言ってんだ　こいつ。
だぅ～！だぅ～！
Hey! What have you done to my girlish face?!
ちょっとぉ～　さっきから
乙女の顔を…。
Come on, people are still...
（美破）こらぁ　まだ人が…。
うるせ～！
Shut up!
ふぅ…やっと静かになった。
Finally, peace and quiet.
アゥー！
おっ　ベル坊も機嫌なおしたか。
Oh? Feeling better yourself, Baby Beel?
Good. I spilled a little blood
for you, so no more crying, 'kay?
よしよし　ちょっと
血ぃ流したぐらいで→
もう泣くんじゃねえぞ。
ダ！
さてと　んじゃ　続きやろうか。
Now then... Let's continue where we left off.
I've lost.
私の負けよ。→
いえ　そうじゃないわ　ごめんなさい
私　何て言っていいか…。
Or, well... That's not right.
I apologize.
What should I say?
そうか　じゃあ　はい。
Oh? Then, here.
ダーブ。
え？
If I withstood your attacks,
you'd agree to take him, right?
だって　お前の攻撃に
耐えきったら→
こいつのこと
もらってくれるんだろ？
Where'd that rule come from?
（寧々・邦枝）なに　そのルール！？
Man, that was pretty tough.
いや～　なかなかきつかったぜ。
う～む　出るに出られなかったが
これは　まずい。→
I wasn't able to jump in
before, but this is dangerous!
Their misunderstanding is cleared
up, and they're making up!
誤解が解けて仲直り
２人の仲は　より親密に！
The two of them'll get really close!
クソー！何で男鹿ばっかり。
がっかりだよ！
Crap! Why is it always
Oga who gets the chicks?!
Indeed.
全くだ　あの男には失望した。
I'm highly disappointed in that man.
And I had thought his ruthlessness
was his one redeeming value.
残忍なだけが取り柄だと
思っておったのに…。
So he won't fight a woman, will he?
女相手では　手も上げんのか。
まったくもって　クズめ。
Worthless piece of trash.
あの　もしかして
ずっと後ろにいました？
Um... Were you behind me the whole time?
Yes.
うむ　貴様の「よしよし　もっとやれ」
というつぶやき　心にしみたぞ。
Your hushed whispers of "Yes, that's
it! Do him harder!" stirred my heart.
あぁ～　やめて～！！
Please don't!
And that's that. Hope you enjoy him.
そ～ゆ～わけで　よろしく頼むわ。
アダ！
W-Wait a second!
ちょ…ちょっと待って。
もらうって→
Take him? But he's yours, right?
その子　あんたの子でしょ？
あん？オレの子なわけ　ねえだろ。
He's not my kid, duh!
I've just been forced to
raise him, that's all.
無理やり押し付けられて
育ててるだけだぜ。
アダ！
Then the blond woman... She's not your wife?
じゃあ　あの金髪の人は？
奥さんじゃ…。
全然ちがう。
じゃ　一体何なんだよ？
Not even close.
Then who the hell is she?
何って　つまり…悪魔だよ　悪魔。
How should I put this...
She's a total demon.
A demon!?
悪魔！？
《の　ような女！》
...a devil woman!
オーホホ…。
How much longer are you going
to waste spouting nonsense?
いつまで下らん話をしている。
We're going home.
帰るぞ　その女は親にはなりえん。
え～！？いや　でも…。
That woman will not become the parent.
But...
さあ坊っちゃま　帰りましょうね。
アイ　ダーブー。
Now, Master, let's go home.
Hey! Hold it!
おい　ちょっと待て　こら！
待ちなさい！
Wait!
あなた　恥ずかしくないの？
自分の子を人に押しつけたりして。
Aren't you embarrassed?
Forcing another person
to care for your child...
フン　文句があるなら
腕を磨いて　出直してくるんだな。
If you have a problem with it, train
yourself and come at me again.
So in the end, this time was no use either.
結局　今回もダメだったな。
Don't worry, Furuichi. I'm not giving up.
心配するな古市　オレは諦めん。
Wait a moment, Madame
Aoi! What are you saying?
（寧々）待って下さいよ姐さん
何言ってるんすか！
Isn't it obvious? My head wasn't on straight
and I ended up causing everyone trouble.
（邦枝）
当然よ　私が浮わついたせいでみんなに迷惑かけたんだもの。
だからって
何もやめなくても…。
But, you don't have to quit...
Come on, Chiaki, say something!
ほら　千秋も何か言って！似合います！
I like your new look!
Chiaki!
千秋…。
（邦枝）それに　前々から
考えてたことなのよ。→
And besides, I've been thinking
about it for a while.
It was about time to leave
the Red Tails to you, Nene.
そろそろレッドテイルは　寧々に
任せても　いいんじゃないかって。
Madame Aoi!
姐さん！
（邦枝）だから
勘違いしないでよね！
So don't be getting any strange thoughts!
ケジメよ！
Next time we settle this!
あ…。
（寧々）あ　姐さ～ん！
Madame Aoi!
＜毎晩　夜８時になると…＞
Every night, when the clock strikes 8,
８時だよ！
（ＭＫ５）ＭＫ５！
It's 8 o'clock!
MK-5.
（古市）まだ８時じゃねえよ！
It ain't 8 yet!
Well then, what is on next week's Beelzebub?
Hello, I am Oga Tatsumi's father.
It's my first preview, so
I'm a little nervous...
Ah yes, I suppose I don't have a name yet.
Even Furuichi's little sister,
Honoka, has a name...
Oh right, next week's Beelzebub:
Baby Beel's Assessment Test, and
Hilda: Dear Great Demon Lord.
It's a two parter.
Please watch next week as well.
That's all, folks.
Stop right there!